Narrator: people
Speaker 1: Somebody has taken my pen!
Someone has taken my pen!
Speaker 2: I didn’t speak to anybody all weekend.
I didn’t speak to anyone all weekend.
Speaker 1: Did anybody phone?
Did anyone phone?
Speaker 2: No, nobody.
Nobody phoned.
No, no one.
No one phoned.
Narrator: things
Speaker 1: I bought something for dinner.
Speaker 2: I didn’t do anything at the weekend.
Speaker 1: Is there anything in the fridge?
Speaker 2: No, nothing.
There’s nothing in the fridge.
Narrator: places
Speaker 1: Let’s go somewhere this weekend.
Speaker 2: We didn’t go anywhere this summer.
Speaker 1: Is there anywhere to park?
Speaker 2: No, nowhere.
There’s nowhere to park.